Hey guys, it's me, Amienza, and the kitties, and we are having a non-Christmas Christmas
today.
So if for whatever reason you just want some folks to hang out with, for a $5 subscription
to the SEAL Squad, you can hang out with us.
We have programming 12, 4, and 8 p.m. Eastern today that you can be in community.
So join us.
Again, it's a $5 subscription for the entire month.
So you don't just get today's events, but you also get all the content that's been there
previously, as well as access to all of the content and community for the month.
And if you decide to continue, then you continue.
Regardless, nobody should have to be alone on this day that is forced down our throats
and where we are shamed if we don't have family or if we just don't want to celebrate it or
if we don't celebrate it for other reasons.
You feel me?
So come and hang.
See you there.